[Music]
fwd hong kong's most youthful insurance
company was preparing to launch their
series of retirement products
but there was just one problem
young people don't think about
retirement why
because youth is active passionate
vibrant
fun and exciting and retirement is
passive dull and boring
right wrong
we tend to think that retirement is this
momentous step in life
where everything changes but guess what
life just continues a fun person will
always be fun
a passionate person will always be
passionate
and you will continue to be you
born as our idea passion never retires
[Music]
yaudi
[Applause]
[Music]
we wanted to show hong kong that
retirement if anything
is the time to go nuts on what you are
passionate about
and planning for retirement is no
different from planning your weekend
just way in advance accompanying our
campaign was a microsite and retirement
calculator
that takes a more human approach to the
math and numbers
asking consumers to really listen to
their hearts
because times may pass appearances may
fade
but passion passion lives on